[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of all the invertebrates, which has the best eyesight?", "correct_answer": "octopus", "incorrect_answers": ["plankton", "whale", "squid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What name is used for the social groups that chinchillas form when living in the wild?", "correct_answer": "Herds", "incorrect_answers": ["Schools", "Flocks", "Troops"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was Back to the Future Part I initially set?", "correct_answer": "1985", "incorrect_answers": ["1986", "1984", "1982"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these items is more valuable as far as meeting the requirements for 3-D Gaming is concerned?", "correct_answer": "PCI Express video card", "incorrect_answers": ["HDMI 1080p", "Bluetooth", "Integrated (or on board) video"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of doctor is the doctor in the movie 3:10 to Yuma?", "correct_answer": "A veterinarian", "incorrect_answers": ["a dentist", "A baby doctor", "a coroner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which geographical term describes a geological formation that slopes down from the center in all directions?", "correct_answer": "Quaquaversal", "incorrect_answers": ["Quean", "Quassia", "Quartan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the demon haunting Danas apartment in the 1984 sience fiction comedy Ghostbusters?", "correct_answer": "Zuul", "incorrect_answers": ["Caesar", "Chester", "Akasha"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a bibliopole?", "correct_answer": "Someone who sells books", "incorrect_answers": ["Someone who buys books", "Someone who loves books", "Someone who hates books"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which cat is the co-author of Rita Mae Browns Mrs. Murphy series?", "correct_answer": "Sneaky Pie Brown", "incorrect_answers": ["Cleopatra", "Little Guy", "Mrs. Calabash"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of mammal is the Culpeo?", "correct_answer": "Wild dog", "incorrect_answers": ["Beaver", "Wild cat", "Fox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the Hubble Space Telescope put into orbit by the Space Shuttle?", "correct_answer": "1990", "incorrect_answers": ["1991", "1992", "1993"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how many miles per year can the North American caribou travel?", "correct_answer": "3,000", "incorrect_answers": ["11,000", "1,000", "7,000"]}]